// flashcards/envoytest2024.js
export const envoytest2024 = [
	{ front : `A "High Minimum Captain" is a pilot who has not accumulated ______ as a Pilot in command in revenue service on the type aircraft being operated.`, back: `100 Hours` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym IAP stand for?`, back: `<b>I</b>nstrument <b>A</b>pproach <b>P</b>rocedure` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym METAR stand for?`, back: `<b>M</b>eteorological <b>A</b>erodrome <b>R</b>eport` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym TAF stand for?`, back: `<b>T</b>erminal <b>A</b>rea <b>F</b>orecast` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym ASOS stand for?`, back: `<b>A</b>utomated <b>S</b>urface <b>O</b>bserving <b>S</b>ystem` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym IFR stand for?`, back: `<b>I</b>nstrument <b>F</b>light <b>R</b>ules` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym ILS stand for?`, back: `<b>I</b>nstrument <b>L</b>anding <b>S</b>ystem` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym NOTAM stand for?`, back: `<b>Not</b>ice to <b>A</b>ir<b>m</b>en` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym CAVOK stand for?`, back: `<b>C</b>eiling <b>a</b>nd <b>V</b>isibility <b>OK</b>AY` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym SIGMET stand for?`, back: `<b>Sig</b>nificant <b>Met</b>eorological Information` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym ARTCC stand for?`, back: `<b>A</b>ir <b>R</b>oute <b>T</b>raffic <b>C</b>ommand <b>C</b>enter` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym PIC stand for?`, back: `<b>P</b>ilot <b>I</b>n <b>C</b>ommand` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym MEL stand for?`, back: `<b>M</b>inimum <b>E</b>quipment <b>L</b>ist` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym AIRMET stand for?`, back: `<b>Air</b>man's <b>Met</b>eorological Information` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym FROPA stand for?`, back: `<b>Fro</b>ntal <b>Pa</b>ssage` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym RVSM stand for?`, back: `<b>R</b>educed <b>V</b>ertical <b>S</b>eparation <b>M</b>inimum` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym RVR stand for?`, back: `<b>R</b>unway <b>V</b>isual <b>R</b>ange` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym ARFF stand for?`, back: `<b>A</b>icraft <b>R</b>escue and <b>F</b>ire <b>F</b>ighting` },
	{ front : `A flight you dispatched, not requiring an alternate is now airborne and subsequently the weather forecast changes while en-route and now the destination airport is forecasted to be alternate required. You don't have enough fuel to add an alternate. Are you required to add an alternate, so the flight can continue?`, back: `NO` },
	{ front : `Embedded thunderstorm, surface winds greater than 50kts, hail at surface greater than/equal to ¾, tornadoes, line of thunderstorms is an advisory known as?`, back: `A convective SIGMET` },
	{ front : `What does the acronym ICAO stand for?`, back: `<b>I</b>nternational <b>C</b>ivil <b>A</b>viation <b>O</b>rganization` },
	{ front : `What do you do to a High Minimum Captain at the Destination?`, back: `Add 100-½` },
	{ front : `What do you do to a High Minimum Captain at an Alternate?`, back: `No less than 300-1` },
	{ front : `True or False: Jet streams travel from east to west in the northern hemisphere`, back: `FALSE` },
	{ front : `Transcribe this NOTAM excerpt:<br>!DWF 06/451 DFW RWY 17C CLSD 3500FT S RWY 17C/35C`, back: `DFW MONTH 06 / 451 ISSUED, DFW Runway 17 Center Closed 3500FT South End Runway 17 Center / 35 Center` },
	{ front : `What 3 things is a flight dispatcher primarily responsible for in accordance with 14CFR 121.533?`, back: `<ul><li><b>Monitoring</b> the progress of the flight</li><li>Issuing information to the PIC for the <b>Safety</b> of the flight</li><li><b>Canceling or Re-dispatching</b> a flight, if the DX or PIC determine the flight cannot operate or continue to operate safely as planned</li></ul>` },
	{ front : `What is a convective SIGMET for?`, back: `Embedded Thunderstorms, Tornados, Squall Lines, Server Thunderstorms` },
	{ front : `When is a destination (Domestic) alternate required?`, back: `<ul><li>+ or - <b>1</b> hour of the ETA</li><p>Weather is below</p><li><b>2000'</b> ceiling, or</li><li><b>3</b> SM Visibility</li></ul>` },
	{ front : `How many ARTCC are in the contiguous United States?`, back: `20` },
	{ front : `True of False: VFR is defined as a ceiling greater than 3,000 feet AGL and visibility greater than 5 miles.`, back: `TRUE` },
	{ front : `How many types of AIRMETs are there? What are they?`, back: `3: Sierra(IMC), Tango(Turbulence), Zulu(Icing)` },
	{ front : `When does a flag always require an alternate?`, back: `Always, unless 6 hours or less and +/-1 hour of eta, the ceiling is above 1500' AGL, or 1500' of the lowest plate mins, or 2000' AGL airport elevation` },
	{ front : `How many types of icing are there? What type?`, back: `3: Rime, Clear, Mixed` },
	{ front : `True or False: A dispatcher/pilot can always plan to use reserve fuel`, back: `FALSE` },
	{ front : `When is a drift-down alternate required?`, back: `When you cannot maintain Method 1` },
	{ front : `When do you need a takeoff alternate and how far can it be?`, back: `When weather is below landing minimums at the departure airport<br>2 Engine - 1 hour, in still air, with 1 engine inoperative` },
	{ front : `If available, RVR can provide reading up to how many sections of a runway and where are they located?`, back: `3: Touchdown, Midpoint, Rollout` },
	{ front : `What are the minimum fuel requirements for 14 CFR Part 121 Domestic Operations?`, back: `Origin to destination, to the most distant alternate if required, 45 mins thereafter at normal cruise consumption` },
	{ front : `What are the minimum fuel requirements for 14 CFR Part 121 Flag Operations?`, back: `Origin to destination, +10% of origin to destination, to the most distant alternate if required, 30 mins thereafter at 1500' above the airport of destination` },
	{ front : `True or False: For airplanes having a seating capacity of more than 50 but less than 101 passengers, 3 flight attendants are required?`, back: `FALSE` },
	{ front : `Fog at the ETA reduces the indefinite ceiling below landing minimums. What do you do?`, back: `Keep it pushing, list an alternate` },
	{ front : `Fog at the ETA reduces the visibility below landing minimums. What do you do?`, back: `Delay the flight` },
	{ front : `What type of hazard is associated with an AIRMET ZULU?`, back: `Icing` },
	{ front : `True or False: The system requirements for an aircraft to operate in RVSM airspace is 2 independent altimeters, 1 altitude reporting system, 2 altitude alert systems, 1 altitude control system`, back: `FALSE<br>Think of 2RAC` },
	{ front : `True or False: AIRMET TANGO is defined as mountain obscuration or IFR ceiling less than 100' and/or visibility less than 3 miles affecting over 50% of the aera at one time`, back: `FALSE` },
	{ front : `To release a flight under IFR operations, current observation, forecasts or a combination there must indicate that the weather at the destination will be?`, back: `At or above landing minimums` },
	{ front : `After takeoff, WX drops below 1-2-3 rule. What do you do?`, back: `Advise the pilot, issue necessary information for safety of the flight` },
	{ front : `Do you require an alternate if your ETA is 18/1230z?<p style="font-size: 20px; text-align: left; justify-content: center;  font-weight: bold">KDFW 180753Z 1808/1908 15006KT P6SM VCTS SCT025 BKN060 BKN120<br>FM181100 15008KT P6SM SCT020 OVC060<br>TEMPO 1812/1813 3SM TSRA BR SCT002 BKN020CB<br>FM181500 16012KT 5SM -RA VCTS SCT030 OVC045</p>`, back: `NO` },
	{ front : `True or False: A dispatcher and captain do not need to agree on anything that pertain to a flight plan`, back: `FALSE` },
	{ front : `A PAX is very sick on an aircraft inflight. What do you do?`, back: `Patch in STATMD, listen and gather information` },
	{ front : `How many categories of MEL's are there? What are they?`, back: `<p>4: A, B, C, D</p>` },
	{ front : `Can any MEL categories be extended? If yes, which ones?`, back: `Yes. B and C can be extended` },
	{ front : `What is the repair time for MEL category A?`, back: `Must be repaired within the time specified in remarks` },
	{ front : `What is the repair time for MEL category B?`, back: `3 days to repair` },
	{ front : `What is the repair time for MEL category C?`, back: `10 days to repair` },
	{ front : `What is the repair time for MEL category D?`, back: `120 days to repair` },
	{ front : `Except when in cruise flight, below what altitude are non-safety related cockpit activities by flight crewmembers prohibited?`, back: `10,000'` },
	{ front : `What altitudes is RVSM airspace?`, back: `FL290-FL410` },
	{ front : `C-055 Explain: Two NAVAID`, back: `2 different approaches, 2 different NAVAID ID's, adding 200'-½ to the highest landing minimums` },
	{ front : `C-055 Explain: One NAVAID`, back: `1 approach, 1 NAVAID ID, adding 400'-1 to landing minimums` },
	{ front : `True or False: Airborne weather radar is installed to help crew penetrate between severe weather cells`, back: `TRUE` },
	{ front : `On a METAR, what is the difference between CLR and SKC?`, back: `Clear: AO2 Systems provide information for no layers up to 12,000'<br>SKC: is by a human observer` },
	{ front : `A TAF includes "WS020/24040KT" What does this mean?`, back: `Wind Shear, 2000' 240° @ 40kts` },
	{ front : `A TAF includes "BECMG" What does this mean?`, back: `Becoming, a gradual shift` },
	{ front : `A TAF includes "PROB30" What does this mean?`, back: `30% chance of happening during the indicated times` },
	{ front : `What is an ILS?`, back: `<b>I</b>nstrument <b>L</b>anding <b>S</b>ystem (GLAM), Radio Navigation Systems` },
	{ front : `Your captain wants more fuel and you already put a reasonable amount of fuel on board. Balls in your court...`, back: `Sure captain! Provide more fuel within weight limitations` },
	{ front : `Your captain does not want to go in an aircraft which maintenance says is fine. What do you do?`, back: `Contact MX Control, if not happy, contact Chief Pilot` },
	{ front : `What is Method 1?`, back: `At the point of engine failure, you drift down and maintain 1000’ clearance over critical obstacles<br>(Mostly Mountain Peaks)` },
	{ front : `What is Method 2?`, back: `At the point of engine failure, you drift down clearing a critical obstacle by 1000’ and drift down into a valley requiring a drift down alternate` },
];